{
    "questions": [
    { "question": "Which country speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Portugal", "Mexico", "China", "Japan"], "answer": "Mexico" },
    { "question": "Which country speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Spain", "Brazil", "India", "France"], "answer": "Spain" },
    { "question": "Which country speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Venezuela", "Vietnam", "Russia", "Nigeria"], "answer": "Venezuela" },
    { "question": "Which country doesn’t speak Spanish?", "options": ["Mexico", "Portugal", "Venezuela", "Spain"], "answer": "Portugal" },
    { "question": "Which country doesn’t speak Spanish?", "options": ["Columbia", "El Salvador", "Equatorial Guinea", "Sweden"], "answer": "Sweden" },
    { "question": "Which country doesn’t speak Spanish?", "options": ["Nicaragua", "Argentina", "Panama", "Singapore"], "answer": "Singapore" },
    { "question": "Which is the only country in Africa that speaks Spanish?", "options": ["Equatorial Guinea", "Madagascar", "Egypt", "Chad"], "answer": "Equatorial Guinea" },
    { "question": "Name the only country that speaks Spanish in North America", "answer": "Mexico" },
    { "question": "Name the only country that speaks Spanish in Europe", "answer": "Spain" },
    { "question": "How many countries speak Spanish?", "answer": "21 countries" }

    ]
}
   
